Professor...
You're getting married, aren't you?
This wedding is something
I have agreed to, of course.
Even though the person
you're marrying... is Charles Arbor?
Then, will you marry me instead, Rio?
Or will you take me somewhere and
live the rest of your life with me?
Celia...
I am...
a doll.
Halt!
Seize him!
You little...
Who is this guy?
Seize him! Now!
Fall back to the side and
form a single-file wall!
Don't let him get close!
Mage squad, contain him!
Photon Bullet!
This is bad!
Protect the bride and groom!
Enchant Physical Ability!
Encircle and capture him!
Sir!
Everything is fine, Celia.
This is just a nice show before the ceremony.
They are the elite among
the elite of our kingdom,
the chosen few with proven
pedigrees and skills.
No lawless brigand could
possibly hope to topple...
Um...
Seirei Gensouki
Celia!
Count Claire, please wait!
That fool.
Bringing disgrace upon my house...
Duke Arbor!
Unhand me!
The security for this was
supposed to be flawless!
We will do everything we can.
So, please, don't provoke the insurgent.
My lord Count!
Professor Celia...
I apologize for the disturbance,
but while those around us are in turmoil,
I'd like to explain the situation.
If you would keep quiet for a little
while, it would be a great help.
Rio, what is going on?
I am speaking directly into your
consciousness through telepathy.
Focus your words in your mind
and your voice will reach me.
Y-You villain...
What do you want here?
Silence!
I have a grievance with you!
Maybe I'll just go ahead and
crush your spine under my foot!
H-Hold on, Rio!
I won't kill anyone. This is an act,
part of the disturbance.
A-All right...
Why is he... so strong?
We don't have much time.
I'll finish explaining quickly.
Take the guests into the inner sanctum.
Before you are wed, I want to ask
once more, what is your will?
Just for that, you've done all this...
I told you already! I...
I said I want to know your will, Professor.
You're being half-threatened into this
by Duke Arbor's house, aren't you?
What is the security team doing?!
If you wish it, Professor,
I will put an end to this wedding.
You're being domineering!
I know full well that I'm being
domineering and arrogant.
But, Professor, you are precious
to me. I owe you so much.
I don't want to just dstand by
and lose what's important to me!
I know I'd regret it for the rest of my life.
Once something is lost,
it will never come back,
but if you haven't lost it yet,
then there's still time!
I see a future where your dignity will
be trampled on for the rest of your life.
I wouldn't be able stand that.
Professor, will this marriage make you happy?
If I put my own feelings before all else,
I may cause trouble for others.
Would that... be the right thing to do?
I don't know.
But if this wedding were
truly the right thing to do,
then you wouldn't have that look on your face.
Professor, I will make your wish come true.
So, please, don't give up!
If I say I don't want to get married,
what are you planning to do?
I will take you and run away from this place.
That way, no one would question whether
Count Claire was involved, right?
Why would that...
Rio, they'll catch you.
Don't worry. I will make your
wish come true, Professor.
Though that isn't something someone holding
a knife to your throat should be saying.
Rio...
I... want you to take me away.
Leave it to me.
I've decided!
I made up my mind!
Feel the humiliation!
I will abduct your bride
right before everyone's eyes!
Here we go.
Celia!
L-Lord Charles!
C-Celia!
I-I'm so sorry, father.
I promise I'll see you again.
What are you doing? Hurry up and capture him!
All troops, after him!
Hold!
Do not break formation!
You lot, catch him immediately!
Charge!
Sir!
It can't be!
What?
H-Halt!
Wh-What are you doing?
Are you all incompetent?
This was his intent from the beginning.
Didn't you see his jumping
ability when he charged in?
Photon Bullet!
What's this?
I thought he was using some kind
of magic item, but... spirit arts?
Could he have been the one back then...
He's gotten stronger since
the last time I saw him.
In that case, how about this?
Celia!
Impressive.
What are you doing?
Stop firing! What if you hit Celia?
After him! Catch him!
Everyone, listen up!
Our Aerial Knights are now in pursuit.
All forces will now immediately spread
out in a net that encircles the capital!
S-Sir! Right away!
And I will leave the security of
these grounds to you, Vanessa.
Coordinate between the captains of each unit.
Show me how well you keep things moving.
Sir! Understood, Elder Brother!
Alfred!
You've let the raider get away.
Who gave you permission to take command?!
More importantly, do you have any
idea who the insurgent might be?
He said he had a grievance with me.
It sounds like there may be a lot of candidates.
S-Silence!
You go and chase him, too! Immediately!
Catch him and bring him back!
That is my intent.
Well, then...
Blast.
Blast. Blast! Blast him!
This has become quite an
entertaining situation,
but with the protections afforded
to me as an ambassador,
I suppose I shouldn't slip away from here.
I am very interested in him, and that
spirit that never showed itself, though.
W-Wait, Rio!
This is fast. We're going
very fast, aren't we?
Yes. Please be sure to hold on tightly.
I'd rather not deal with griffin unit,
so I'm going to go a little faster.
A-All right.
You've grown into quite an impressive boy.
Thank you very much.
Have you gotten a little
more used to this speed?
Yup! If you can go faster, bring it on!
Huh?
Did you hear that just now, too?
Then I'll take you at your word.
Even if I keep running like this,
it will take time to shake them off,
so we'll head down for a moment.
I'll be passing on the baton,
so we'll meet up again later.
P-Passing on the baton? And what
do you mean, "meet up later"?
It's part of the plan.
The truth is, I have someone helping me.
The girl who first spoke
to you telepathically.
Aishia!
Then, just as we planned it.
Understood.
Wh-What?
Wait! What's going on?
I'll play decoy and buy some time.
Professor, you and she will use this chance
to escape the royal capital together.
I promise I will meet up with you later.
And to explain about this girl...
I'll explain on the way.
That's that.
Look after her for me.
W-Wait, Rio!
I...
Shall we go, Celia?
Yes.
There he is!
But I don't see Lady Celia!
The alley he came out of is a dead end!
Inform the teams on the ground!
Send up a flare!
Sir!
Signal Flare!
They've called for reinforcements.
It's going just as we planned.
All that's left is for me to make
a big show in drawing them away.
Blitz Shot!
He's so quick at evading!
Continue the attack!
Blitz Shot!
Over there! Let's go!
Like I'd let you!
There really are a lot of them.
Don't give him a chance to rest!
Reinforcements are coming.
Let's wear him down as much as we can!
Let's do it!
Not killing anyone...
might be making this tougher.
But...
I just told Professor Celia not to give up.
I can't give up now!
That's as far as you go.
I will now restrain you.
Lord Alfred!
Alfred?
He's the one they call the
King's Sword, isn't he?
You will only add to the number of injured.
All of you, stand back.
Sir!
He's strong.
There's some kind of powerful
magic formula cast on that sword.
L-Lord Alfred is being pushed back...
Why do you not turn your blades on me?
It seems you underestimate me.
But that ends now.
Lord Alfred!
I don't see the insurgent anywhere.
What happened to him?
If he took the full force of the blow,
not a trace of him would be left, but...
I didn't feel it hit him.
And there's evidence he
fled into the back streets.
Just to be sure, search the surrounding area!
And we'll look for Miss Celia as well!
Sir!
Aishia... Rio is all right, isn't he?
He's fine. He's almost here.
Aishia?
Is he really all right?
I've just returned.
Rio! I'm so glad!
I know I worried you, but everything
is all right now, Professor.
Y-Yes.
Rio, you aren't hurt, are you?
No, I'm not.
And Aishia...
Thank you.
Not at all. I didn't do
anything of importance.
Well, shall we go?
Yes.
Is this really all right?
Do you want to go back?
You could still make it in time, but...
What? N-No!
I was just thinking it doesn't
feel real, that's all.
After all, for a moment my future was
so bleak, I thought my life was over.
But you're here with me now, Rio.
Thank you, Rio, for kidnapping me!
You're very welcome.
We'll have to think about
what we're going to do next.
Yes, that's true.
Professor Celia, I have something
I absolutely must do.
But I won't let you suffer for lack of
anything when it comes to daily necessities.
Rest assured on that point.
I see.
Well then, I suppose I'll take
you up on that for a while.
I am inexperienced and inept,
but I hope you will look on me kindly.
I am the one who hopes you
will look on me kindly.
And...
Let's talk a lot to make up for all
the time we didn't see each other!
Yes, let's!
It's coming.
Aishia?
Haruto, please, help them!
What?
I will protect Celia.
Please!
Masato, where are we?
Don't ask me!
W-Well... for now, shall we
try to find out where we are?
No Service
No service?
That hurts!
No!
Masato-kun!
No! Someone, help!
Aki-neechan!
Please, don't do anything
horrible with those children!
You go in a different cart. This way.
One of your guards was carrying this.
What is that thing?
Don't know anything about it.
Someone, help us!
Japanese?
Please! Let us out of here!
Is it just the two of you?
You speak Japanese?
There's one more.
That way we can always be
together, side by side...
Even if I die, I'll protect you, Mii-chan!
Or, do you not want to...
You're...
Th-Thank you so much for saving us.
My name is Ayase Miharu.
Fated Reunion
Spirit Chronicles
Exciting Bonus Manga
You're...
By Minazuki Futago
Yes!
Celia here!
Aishia...
Hiss
Ha ha ha...
It's so lively
here.
Rio
Haruto... I'm sorry, it's too early...
Onii-chan
Seirei Gensouki:
Spirit Chronicles
Thank you for watching